and now for the only true movie star
on this stage me i apparently was
in star wars how high was i when i said
i would do this i'm a generous guy so
sharing the spotlight is my gift to all
of you i am still
[Applause]
what the am i doing here
this is like that moscow hotel room
where a bunch of pissed all over
donald trump
i mean this is what you get for being
alex
friend on nights like these you expect
your friends
the people you've worked with closely to
show up tina fey
tracy morgan thomas the tank engine
meryl streep
[Applause]
not one instead we have a group
you can't even find them on wikipedia
and like who are these people i mean
who the hell are you
ann coulter everybody
nikki is what's known as a dirty
comedian and i don't mean a material i
mean she hasn't washed the since
memorial day
[Applause]
caroline ray oh good one
caroline did over 160 episodes of
sabrina the teenage witch
that's a lot of teenagers not
r kelly numbers but still
pretty impressive
sean hayes we're here over here
[Laughter]
i was in goodfellas and i'm guessing
sean has also been in goodfellas
and some bad fellas
and more than a few sailors i'm sure
caitlyn jenner now there's something
different about you but i i can't
i can't put my finger in it
yes you can
yes you care comedy central wanted to
have caitlyn on a roast
after her surgery so now they can pay
her 20 percent less
[Applause]
when i did raging bull i had to gain 60
pounds in four months
jeff what's your excuse
[Laughter]
kendra john once stopped his stand-up
show to help a woman in the audience who
was having a seizure
if a seizure is what it takes to stop
him from doing stand up on for that
adam carolla adam promotes a drink
called
the brosay cocktail finally a light
refreshing summer drink for date rapists
[Applause]
and now for the only true movie star
on the stage me
critics say i have a unique quality as
an actor
i actually like alec baldwin
and i'm happy to be here for alec but
honestly i'm here to teach chris redd
caitlyn jenner and blake griffin how to
black women
please welcome jonah hill
hi guys james
how's it going it's really great to be
here for my buddy james
um i just don't know why they would
choose me though because there's nothing
really anyone can make fun of me for
i guess these guys are going to make fun
of me for something so
i just think i'm just going to be nice
and say what i like about them because i
i really love all these people up here
you know like bill hader good friend of
mine
right he was brilliant on snl he was
brilliant
and when he left the show this year
every single person was like what are
you doing you're never
ever gonna work again like ever and what
does my man bill do
boom he goes ahead and books himself a
t-mobile commercial
who's laughing now lauren michaels my
man bill is
i mean this guy's cashing checks from
the fourth largest mobile provider
in the nation
look no look i respect bill because
sprint was coming after him hard
but he just held out for that ut mobile
money
bill's awesome
i love you bill andy sandberg
is another friend of mine i love him and
now that he's got his new tv show
brooklyn 99 which i'm assuming is about
this brooklyn cop who tried to make it
in the movie business but failed and got
sent back to tv
um
my only question is andy when the show
gets canceled after five episodes
are you gonna do a different cell phone
commercial are they gonna turn bills
into a two-hander for both of you guys
andy's awesome
sarah silverman so amazing
so beautiful i think you're gorgeous and
i think it's crazy because
everyone's like she's hot for a comic
but i don't agree because she's not just
hot for a comic she's hot for someone
her age
that's right um
seriously sarah you were my favorite
comic as a kid um
and people say it's too late for sarah
to become successful in movies at her
age
i again do not agree it's not impossible
i mean it's not like they're asking you
to bear children or anything like that
because you can't do that
we got ludacris we got my man snoop dogg
shack this is crazy usually when i see
this many brothers sitting together
mari pover just about to open the
envelope i've never seen anything like
that
[Laughter]
shaq take that dumb ass look over your
face you look stupid
[Laughter]
[Applause]
here's my question how did you even end
up on a roast
that's what i want to know they must
have called up the nba proof game show
and said you know what
send us the third funniest guy
wait he's unavailable send a shack let
us get shaq then
uh my man snoop dogg is here there he is
yeah wait wait
let me clear something up for all the
young people here tonight uh snoop
snoop dogg is a rapper uh
yeah that's my aunt's favorite rapper
you know
for all the black people that are
confused about that old white woman on
the couch that's martha stewart
yeah right there that's martha stewart
right there
martha do me a favor and uh put your
ankle bracelet on vibrate so we don't
have no problems
doing the show what a night
you've all talked about me berating the
paparazzi marrying a woman half my age
and so many other memorable achievements
i'm glad you all had fun and a sizable
amount of tv exposure at my expense but
just
there's one more charitable act that
i've done that i won't get credit for
i'm a generous guy so sharing the
spotlight is
my gift to all of you
at the same time i want to set all of
you straight not you sean if your father
couldn't do that how can i
[Applause]
sean you have the face of a
ventriloquist doll and the of a
much larger ventriloquist style
[Laughter]
blake griffin my gift to you is bringing
awareness to whatever tragic skin
disease it is you have you're a
remarkable man blake
i wish we were as close as your eyes are
blake griffin tonight you demonstrated
what you do best sitting while others
score
we're all learning that's all we can do
i didn't even know what a nicki glazer
was before tonight i still don't
you the flight attendant i was rude to
i'm sorry if you were
but i don't regret finishing my game of
words with friends on that flight
i sniped an incredible 92-pointer with
zymergy
zymergy bob isn't that your second
wife's name
[Applause]
no wait no wait it's the medication jeff
ross takes for losing his battle with
seepage
[Applause]
what devastating comment could i make
about nikki glazer that she hasn't
already muttered to herself
in a mirror at equinox
caroline ray caroline i just love you
you are so open and honest
backstage she told all of us she hasn't
been laid in so long
she went through caitlyn jenner's trash
looking for dick
but you were great tonight you have a
great time this is the longest you've
gone without mentioning sabrina the
teenage witch
true story caroline visited my sick
mother when she was dying of cancer in
the hospital
we sat for a bit and then she turned on
the tv and said sabrina the teenage
witches on
caroline you totally get the assist on
that suicide
my mom attacked that morphine button
like she was trying to buzz in on
jeopardy
ken jong i'm proud of you normally you
come across like an asian stereotype but
tonight
your lips totally match the words you
were saying
i'm such a fan of your work the way you
flipped that shrimp tail into your hat
on my birthday was just genius
i realized i'm not very big in the asian
community but i suppose there's a good
reason
the hardest possible title for you to
pronounce is glenn gary glenn ross
my name is seth rogan welcome to the
comedy central roast
of james franco why uh
why are we here why are we doing this
anyway i'll start with the jewish and
work my way down sarah silverman is here
sarah and i actually worked together on
the film take this waltz
uh which she was great in she actually
did full frontal nudity in the movie
uh which was fantastic it was
amazing i always thought she was very
liberal but it turns out she's actually
a giant bush supporter
huge aziz ansari is here
yes this is actually the longest aziz
has ever heard me talk without checking
to see if someone more famous has texted
him
i want to make fun of you for being
friends with kanye west but truthfully
it's the only cool thing there is about
you so i can't do that
jonah hill is here
a lot of people compare jonah to a young
belushi
jim belushi
[Applause]
jonas actually started to move away from
comedy uh it happens five minutes into
his movie the sitter
andy sandberg is here
and he plays a cop on his new fox show
his first case will be investigating the
disappearance of his new fox show
a lot of people are live tweeting the
show tonight speaking of 140 characters
no one gives a about bill hader is
here
bill's a great impressionist right now
he's doing an impression of a guy who
really regrets leaving snl
nick kroll is here
yes nick kroll is the scary jewish face
mel gibson runs from in his dreams every
night
[Applause]
let's start talking about someone people
actually give a about james franco
uh
you know who is the real james franco
is he an artist is he an actor is he a
scholar
he's tough to pin down although i've
heard many guys have been able to do it
i learned two things tonight bumping
into seth green
backstage he is a big star wars fan
and i apparently was in star wars
so amazing
that must have been great uh you know
now uh wayne brady
how are you you're so white that i
i tried to snort you backstage didn't i
i'm sorry
wow now uh i have seen
gilbert gottfried at 12 step meetings
uh you know he was not actually there
they uh they held a picture
up of him and they said if you
this man a how humiliating for you
and b you must be an alcoholic
uh at least i hope so
buckle up this is ass whooping
time
that's what i'm talking about you know
in my action movies there's always some
young punk
trying to come at me and tonight it's
judas
gordon levitt
joe i took you under my wing
tried to make you tough try to make you
an action star
which ain't easy to do with the kid who
looks like the bad boy
of figure skating
[Applause]
joseph played a younger me in looper
couldn't pull it off
there's only one actor who successfully
played me
it was to me more
and she made a lot more money than you
did sweetheart
and now i want to take on the toughest
person up here
my friend ex-con martha stewart
yeah baby if anyone can survive in
prison it's someone who can toss a
salad that's right
martha's a real corporate kingpin
she even has her own brand of wine it's
like her boyfriend
it comes in an old box
martha is also a humanitarian when she
heard about the kids at the border
living in tiny cages
she sent them sewing machines
what's wrong with that kevin
welcome to the party pal you owe your
whole
career to the guys you impersonate
you've made more
money doing schwarzenegger than his maid
and not to mention you're better at
cleaning houses
and finally it's so great to have the
esteemed
diplomat dennis rodman here
i don't want to say dennis is a bad
negotiator but he thinks a shoe deal is
when you get two
at the same time venice how do you and
kim jong-un communicate when neither of
you speak english
dennis i know you think it's a big deal
that you saved the world but it's not
as much as it's made up to be who cares
i've saved the world 18
times nothing can keep me down i've been
attacked by terrorists
asteroids film critics music critics
restaurant critics divorce lawyers
male pattern baldness and none of it
none of it stopped me because i am still
bruce
willis
people ask me why i did this first
was it because one of the last guys who
did it became president
hell no why would i want to be president
when i can
just keep being bruce willis
i did this rose for one reason and for
one reason only
to settle something once and for all
now please listen very carefully
die hard is not
a christmas movie
a goddamn bruce willis movie
so a yippie kaye to all of you
good night
[Applause]
you